
const questions = [
    {
        id: "1",
        question:"Assessment ID/Assessment Name is not getting generated",
        answer : "",
        bullets:[
                    " Go to Farming level data screen. ",
                    " Input Farm name, field, crop name, and year of assessment to generate an Assessment ID/Assessment Name Click on the Save button"
    
            ] 
    },
    {
        id:"2",
        question: "How to Add another Field in the Carbon Calculation platform.",
        answer: "",
        bullets:[
                    " Go to Farming Level Data Screen",
                    " Click Add Another Field Button",
                    "Enter the appropriate information in prompted questions",
                    "Click on the Save button",
                    "Repeat steps to add an additional field"
          ]
    },
     {
        id:"3",
        question: "Carbon footprint screen is not showing any Carbon footprint value",
        answer: "Double-check that all mandatory information has been provided"
    },
    {
        id: "4",
        question: "In Carbon footprint result screen Farm/Field data in not match with user inputs/values",
        answer: "Make sure you have saved all information added. If the problem still persists, please reach out to   support@authen.com"
    },
    {
        id:"5",
        question: "I can't change the unit of measurement possible cause?",
        answer: "Please clean your browser Cache and try again. If the issue still persists, please reach out to support@authen.com. Depends on browser, codebase,"
    },
    {
        id:"6",
        question: "How to Add multiple Fertilizers",
        answer: " ",
        bullets:[
                  " Click on the Add Fertilizer button",
                  " Enter appropriate information in prompted questions",
                  " Click on the Save button",
                  "Repeat steps to add an additional fertilizer "
       ]
    },
    {
        id:"7",
        question: "How to Add multiple Nutrients",
        answer:" ",
        bullets:[
                  " Click on the Add Nutrients button",
                  "Enter the appropriate information in prompted questions",
                  "Click on the Save button",
                  "Repeat steps to add additional nutrients"
       ]
    },
    {
        id:"8",
        question: "How to Add multiple Energy",
        answer:" ",
        bullets:[
                 " Click on the Add Energy button",
                 "Enter the appropriate information in prompted questions",
                 "Click on the Save button",
                 " Repeat steps to add additional energy"
       ]
    },
    {
        id:"9",
        question: "I like to add new items in dropdowns (LOV). The type of refrigerant/Energy/Fertilizer/Nutrients/feed I used is not listed here.",
        answer: "Please reach out to support@authen.com"
    },
    {
        id:"10",
        question: "Potential Value is not showing",
        answer:" ",
        bullets:[
                   "Change the Potential Value inputs",
                   "Click the Recalculate button to see the potential value"
        ]
    },
    {
        id:"11",
        question: "I can't add decimal values possible cause?",
        answer: "Please clean your browser Cache, if the issue still persists, please reach out to support@authen.com. Depends on browser, codebase,"
    },
    {
        id:"12",
        question: "Graph is not displaying correct Carbon Emission source specific value",
        answer: "Please reach out to support@authen.com"
    },
    {
        id:"13",
        question: "Carbon footprint result is showing a big discrepancy to a 3rd party calculator",
        answer:" ",
        bullets:[
                   " A unique combination of standards and formulas for our algorithm, we do not have information on how other platforms designed their algorithm.",
                   "Hence, we cannot comment on discrepancies to a 3rd party calculator"
        ]
    },
    {
        id:"14",
        question: "Carbon footprint result not showing up in individual stage (Supply Chain Module)",
        answer:" ",
        bullets:[
                    " Double-check that all required data has been entered",
                    " Click on the Save button"
        ]
    },
    {
        id:"15",
        question: "The save tab is not working on the carbon calculator page",
        answer: "Please reach out to support@authen.com"
    },
    {
        id:"16",
        question: "The Summary page is not showing all user inputs/Values properly",
        answer: "Make sure you have saved all information added. If the problem still persists, please reach out to support@authen.com"
    },
    {
        id:"17",
        question: "The Add Information link is not working",
        answer: "Please clean your browser Cache and try again, if the issue still persists, please reach out to support@authen.com."
    }
    ]
    
    
    
    
    
    